

**Hudson Kennedy** FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### CONTACT

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



### ABOUT ME

Graduated in Management Processes, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I have always had the desire to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally, I got in touch with the technology area about 10 years ago and since the end of 2019, I have returned to the technology area. where I've been studying and taking different courses. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I have learned many new things and evolved day by day.

I will continue to improve myself daily as a Front-end Developer and Software Engineer after graduation, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Full Technical Consultant** 

January 2022 - April 2022

providing services for Porto, CVC and etc.

Adobe Experience Manager(AEM),

Fullstack Consulting, working with Java in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend,

**VILT Brazil Information Systems** 

using Platform programs

Appen Projects/99Freelas/Capitona Rio I did some freelance work, using Angular Js, Angular 7+, Jquery with **Bootstrap and Sass** 

Freelancers/Personal Works

February 2019 - at moment

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

February 2019 - June 2021

**DT3 Sports** 

Invoice issuance, marketplaces, content creation for campaigns, website development in React.JS, image optimization and responsible for the integration of ERP Bling.

Office Assistant

November 2014 - June 2018

**Nova Lik Auto Peças** 

Issuance of Sales Invoice **Issuance of Payment Reports** Input and Output of Products in Stock.

Quality and Service Technician

June 2010 - July 2013

**Arcos Dourados LTDA.** 

Make employees work coordinated in their respective functions. for better customer service and delivery of a 100% qualitative product.



# ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Faculdade Única

2021 - 2022

MBA Software Engineering

Estácio de Sá - RJ 2018 - 2020

**TECHNOLOGIST** Management processes



Hudson Kennedy
FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

### CONTACT

Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hudsonkennedyjr/

Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



HTML/CSS/Jquery/Javascript/Angular/React/VueJs/NodeJs
4 Years of Experience
Git/Github/NPM/YARN/Wordpress/Shopify/Bling
4 Years of Experience
Bootstrap/Typescript/UI-UXDesinger/Figma/Photoshop
3 Years of Experience
Less/Sass/TailwindCss
1 Year of Experience
PHP/Laravel/Docker/Webpack

## EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

DIO - Components, Methods and Lifecycle with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Component Properties and Directives with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - 2022

DIO - Working with SPA Pages with Angular - 2022

DIO - Working with Components in React - 2022

DIO - Component architecture and front-end complexity - 2022 Adobe Professional – AEM Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional - AEM Front-End Developer - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS -

FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

1 Month of Experience

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/

NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ - Udemy - 2020



#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - Basic French - Basic Italian - Basic English - Advanced



#### ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel/Word /Power Point
Teams/Outlook/Skype
Wordpress/Shopify/ERP Bling
System Configurations
Windows
Computer Domain
Typing
Document Archiving
Internet in general
Google Chrome/Mozilla/Opera